{
    "id": "665c30aae8c64ec8ab4fef4175994e69",
    "title": "Would vs. Should",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Janet ……………………. be here soon.",
            "description": "We use should to indicate possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80445d137fed4f4b938d9d8c3da7b16e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I turn the heating on?",
            "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion.",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf6e707ab8e14c7598e17b63f580c4a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………… be invited to the party.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "23d44b055aee499c9ce89cc3da03e4f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "People ………………………. obey traffic laws.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f39d3d33d32d456db8ce447e492dc0a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… say things like that to Granny.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "shouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79a234ec897c4812aa3024921cb12ba0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. call if I arrived early.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "288016b2a4884b669e1f34e78d3abaea"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. be grateful if you could help me.",
            "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ab109a25e9044f19e43a63cc4f61865"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you like something to drink?",
            "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d48c5a5af5994a0e93e9ae0351736c58"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. I talk to the manager?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22a4579a53d446c6839f044a4cab7d75"
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew that I ………………………… stop hating her, but it seemed rather difficult.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e509a1214c44e6db24a17c9cad2b464"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. have sent the parcel this morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f451cb53f664ced987f3de2cfda6c45"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. have wasted so much time on this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would not",
                "should not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce3496db53c04068bf90216cd366a381"
        }
    ]
}